

## CONTACT

9

Vetapalem, Andhra Pradesh



sivasaikumar.pinjala@gmail.com



+91 9573654644



Siva Sai Kumar



sivasaikumarssk

## **EDUCATION**

Full Stack Web-Development

Masai School, Bangalore.

October 2021 - Present.

B.Tech (Mechanical)

Godavari Institute of Engineering &

Technology

September 2014 - March 2018.

## **SKILLS & FRAMEWORKS**

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React | Mongo DB | express | Node Js

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Quick Learner | Adaptability | Flexible to work under Pressure

## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

**Team Captain** Zonal level Basketball January 2018

## **INTERESTS**

Basketball | Cricket | Reading Books

# PINJALA SIVA SAI KUMAR

#### **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Enthusiastic full-stack web-developer with a specialization in MERN stack. Interested in building user-centric products and creative websites. Looking forward to join a company where I can utilize my skills and learn new skills whilst contributing to the growth of the organization.

#### **PROJECTS**

## Tanishq 🗘

A web application where you can shop a wide range of Jewellery items

#### Features:

- Responsive navbar which displays different categories on hover on the navbar.
- Responsive Footer where you can find the details of the website.
- Users can easily buy products and pay easily through the payment gateway.

Tech Stack: HTML | CSS | JavaScript

## Areas of responsibility:

- Took the Card details and stored them on Local storage.
- Built a Payment gateway.
- Developed a Safe & secure payment process.

A collaborative project built by a team of 5 members executed in 5 days.

## Tata 1MG 🕠

A web application clone where you can buy various medicines and health products.

#### Features:

- Home page built with a lot of dropdown CSS properties.
- Authentication for login and signup.
- Home page with pixel perfect as the same as the original website.
- Cart page functionalities.

Tech Stack: HTML | CSS | JavaScript

A solo project executed in 5 days.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Isuzu Motors India Private Limited

Graduate Engineer Trainee

January 2019 - January 2020

- Worked in the production line of 20members where I had to look after production line activities like TPM, work time.
- Worked on production planning based on the requirement and tack time.
- Cost preparation(NPM) and Quality control.

## Unicharm India Private Limited

Supervisor

October 2020 - December 2020

- Allocated tasks to the team and tracked the daily work reports
- Updated the KPI of employees regularly along with the production details.